{
    "subject": "Paul_Spence",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "FUBAR__film_",
    "human_readable": "Paul Spence created the film FUBAR.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.783758282661438,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Paul Spence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6871311664581299,
            "question": "Who directed the film FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.661665141582489,
            "question": "Is FUBAR a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6030667424201965,
            "question": "What other works has Paul Spence created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5903843641281128,
            "question": "What type of work did Paul Spence create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.499658465385437,
            "question": "Has Paul Spence won any awards for his work on FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42810168862342834,
            "question": "What is the plot of FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37600600719451904,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35662999749183655,
            "question": "What year was FUBAR released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3277634084224701,
            "question": "Where was FUBAR filmed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Spence created the film FUBAR.",
            "html": "yago_10054_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was FUBAR released?",
            "html": "yago_10054_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the actors in FUBAR?",
            "html": "yago_10054_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of FUBAR?",
            "html": "yago_10054_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10054_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The document mentions \"Paul Spence\" as an actor who plays the character Dean in the film Fubar.\n* It also mentions that David Lawrence and Paul Spence were involved in creating the film Fubar 2.\n\nGiven this information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention Paul Spence and David Lawrence as the stars of the films \"Fubar\" and \"Fubar 2,\" indicating that they are involved in creating these films. While the exact role is not specified, the context suggests their involvement in the creation or performance in the film, which supports the statement that Paul Spence created the film FUBAR."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}